gloryholegirlz.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy

This Policy explains what information we collect about you and what we do with it. We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, and we will post any new policy here. You should return to this Policy often to see if it has changed. By using or navigating any of the Sites, you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by this Policy or any modified Policy as posted. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, please do not use or visit any of our Sites.

**What information do we collect?**

We collect personal information that you provide to us such as your name, e-mail address, street address and telephone number. We generally collect this personal information on our registration and order forms when you sign up to receive products or services from any of our Sites.

**What do we do with the information we collect?**

We use personal information and other demographic or profile information you provide to us to fulfill your orders or requests, for security, to provide you with information about our sites and to contact you when necessary.

**Do we share the information we collect with third parties?**

No, all information that is collected is for our use only.

**Is the information submitted in public forums confidential?**

No. The Sites may offer chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or news groups to our users. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas becomes public information. Accordingly, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information and you do so at your own risk.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are pieces of information generated by web servers and stored in your computer for future access. The Sites use cookie technology to enhance your online experience by making it easier for you to navigate through our Sites or make a feature work better.

**Are the Sites secure?**

We are committed to maintaining the security of your information and have measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All credit transactions occur in a secure area of the Site using Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") software to process orders. SSL encrypts the information you input on the Sites. In addition, all information is stored in a secure location behind a firewall with limited administrative access.

**How do I unsubscribe?**

All e-mails you receive from us will include specific instructions on how to unsubscribe and you may unsubscribe at any time. Additionally, you may use any of the following options for removing your information from our database:

(1) Send an email to 

[ webmaster@thestall.com](mailto:webmaster@thestall.com)  (please indicate the Site(s) from which you would like to be unsubscribed);

(2) Select the opt-out link at the bottom of any of our emails or newsletters and follow the instructions provided;

(3) Send a letter with your request to the following address (please indicate the Site(s) from which you would like to be unsubscribed):

Customer Service Department  
Web Wizard, Inc.  
PO Box 25332  
Tampa, FL 33622

Please note, however, you cannot opt out of receiving emails from us regarding your account and/or the status of an order.

**Can I update/correct my information?**

Yes. You may correct or update your personal information by sending us an email at 

Your opt out request will be processed within 30 days of the date it was received.
